# Mohamad Abdul Hakim Bin Mohamad

Email me: jamemadisonnn@gmail.com Portfolio: QR-Code Down below **Call me:** +60 11 – 11 38 8445 Address: Mutiara Heights, Kajang, Selangor

**SUMMARY** With 2 years of startup experience, I excel in front-end development, graphic design, and digital marketing. I create captivating websites with user-friendly interfaces using tools such as Wordpress, Webflow or pure HTML & CSS. Up-to-date with trends.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

GlobalTech Retail Solutions - E-commerce Executive; Kuala Lumpur (Feb 2023 – June 2023) As the E-Commerce Executive at GlobalTech Retail Solutions, I led efforts to create and execute e-commerce strategies for revenue growth. I also managed sales across different platforms, including our website, mobile apps, and third-party sites like Lazada and Shopee.

- Collaborated with the marketing team to create targeted online advertising campaigns, leading to a 20% increase in website traffic and a 10% growth in customer acquisition.
- · Stayed up-to-date with industry best practices, attending e-commerce conferences and workshops to bring the latest insights and strategies to our team.

#### Koffielane – Junior Barista; Prima Saujana (Kajang)

(Jul 2022 - Nov 2022)

Efficiently took and prepared orders. Maintained a clean and inviting dining area for guest satisfaction. Delivered excellent customer service, ensuring timely food and beverage delivery. Assisted with dishwashing and restocking for seamless service.

- During peak hours, I efficiently served 4+ cappuccinos every 5 minutes. Single-handedly managing all cafe stations (Cashier, Bakery & Barista) for an hour during understaffed times showcased my multitasking skills. ensuring smooth operations and prompt service.
- I demolished a team of three people by implementing an efficient kitchen-style communication system with my previous manager. Streamlining our processes, we achieved the same productivity and output with just two team members.

**Isadora & Associates – Digital Marketer**; Tamarind Square (Cyberjaya) (Nov 2020 - June 2021) (Other Job Title: Website Maintenance, Graphic Designer, Social Media Manager) lead impactful marketing campaigns, creating compelling content and managing social media platforms to drive customer engagement and boost sales. I also contribute to website maintenance and updates, ensuring a seamless online presence aligned with the firm's goals.

- Developed and implemented a highly effective sales funnel for the sales team that resulted in a significant improvement of +46.03% through streamlined communication and productivity. Leveraged tools like Google Forms and Sheets for optimal results.
- Implemented sales team performance metrics to assess strengths, weaknesses, and provide actionable insights. Analyzed monthly evaluations, communicated findings to enhance staff performance, and drive sales success.

Finland Shield – Business Development Executive; Seksyen 13 (Shah Alam) (*May 2019 – Mar 2020*) (Other Job Title: Digital Marketer, Wordpress Developer, Social Media Manager)

I develop and maintain the company's WordPress sales page, generate valuable leads for the sales team, and oversee day-to-day operations. With design and content skills, I enhance brand presence, captivate audiences, and drive growth.

- Played a significant role in developing a WordPress-based sales page that effortlessly generated over
  +73.94% more sales than the sales team during product launch day.
- Implemented a highly effective advertising strategy that maximized profit while keeping the cost low. Optimized ads campaigns and targeted the right audience through cost-efficient channels, resulting in exceptional results that boosted company profitability while minimizing advertising expenses.

### **7Eleven – Store Clerk**; Ukay Perdana (Selangor)

(Oct 2018 – Apr 2019)

Proficient in cash handling, inventory management, and ensuring product freshness. Specializes in day-to-day shift operations. Responsible for accurate cash balancing and receipt submission.

• I excel in customer interaction, delivering exceptional service and achieving a 12% boost in monthly sales through effective upselling techniques.

**Gstar Nutrilabs** – **Online Sales Executive**; Ukay Perdana (Selangor) (*Dec 2017 – July 2018*) selling products and services through persuasive arguments, Updates and follow-ups prospects on sales, and encouraging positive business relationships to drive continuous sales growth.

• Consistently **surpassed sales targets** for **three consecutive months**, delivering exceptional good results even in challenging market conditions.

#### **EDUCATION**

Maclearn International College | Diploma Of Multimedia Art's Malaysian Certificate of Education (SPM)

(2016-2018)

## **SKILLS & OTHER**

Language: Native Malay speaker, Fluent in English.

Soft Skills: Adaptability, Growth mindset, Leadership, Conflict resolution, Empathy, Active listening,

Problem-solving, Customer Service, Soft Spoken, Communication.

Programming Language: HTML, CSS, (Exceptionally Good) PHP, Python. (Beginner)

**Technical:** Wordpress, Webflow, Vscode, Bootstrap, Figma, MySQL, Github, Adobe illustrator, Premier

Pro, Google Workspace, Microsoft Office.